许多结了婚的夫妻……
A lot of married couples...
我和你爸要分手了
Your father and l are splitting up.
谢天谢地，太好不过了
Thank you. That's great.
我时间有点赶
It was just a matter of time.
我要去拿包裹
I'll go get the bags packed.
要走的时候通知一下
Let me know when we're ready to go.
布兰登，你就不能坐下呆一会儿？
Why don't you sit down, Brendan, for a second?
我们想说说我们怎么想的
We'll tell you what we're thinking.
要是你同意的话
You see if you agree.
达成共识？
A consensus?.
天方夜谭，好吧
That's novel. Okay.
罗伯特：你妈爱上了托尼
ROBERT: Your mother has fallen in love with Tony.
他们决定搬到托尼的公寓里同居，然后……
They're gonna be moving into his apartment for awhile and...
就这样
Yeah.
有人给这房子报了价
We've had an offer on this house.
虽然只有房价的一半，不过我们准备卖了
It's half what it's worth, but we're gonna take it.